[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Tell me how you're feeling today on this 50th anniversary?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "how", "you", "'re", "feeling", "today", "on", "this", "50th", "anniversary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Well it's been rather emotional.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "it", "'s", "been", "rather", "emotional", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "When you stood at Dealey Plaza, did your mind go back very vividly to what happened 50 years ago?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "stood", "at", "Dealey", "Plaza", ",", "did", "your", "mind", "go", "back", "very", "vividly", "to", "what", "happened", "50", "years", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dealey Plaza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Did you realize immediately that the first shot that impacted on the President was a bullet?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "realize", "immediately", "that", "the", "first", "shot", "that", "impacted", "on", "the", "President", "was", "a", "bullet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Was she reaching back you because you were, I know her personal bodyguard, or was it as I have read elsewhere that she literally can see parts of her husband's head on the back of the limousine?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "reaching", "back", "you", "because", "you", "were", ",", "I", "know", "her", "personal", "bodyguard", ",", "or", "was", "it", "as", "I", "have", "read", "elsewhere", "that", "she", "literally", "can", "see", "parts", "of", "her", "husband", "'s", "head", "on", "the", "back", "of", "the", "limousine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Kennedy"]}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "By this point, did you know for certain that the President was almost definitely dead?", "question_tokens": ["By", "this", "point", ",", "did", "you", "know", "for", "certain", "that", "the", "President", "was", "almost", "definitely", "dead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I was quite sure he was dead because he had fallen into his left and his head was in Mrs. Kennedy's lap.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "quite", "sure", "he", "was", "dead", "because", "he", "had", "fallen", "into", "his", "left", "and", "his", "head", "was", "in", "Mrs.", "Kennedy", "'s", "lap", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Is that correct?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "That is true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", ":", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "What was -- What was it like to be in that limousine for those eight minutes?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "--", "What", "was", "it", "like", "to", "be", "in", "that", "limousine", "for", "those", "eight", "minutes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, when the President was shot that -- shot and hit him in the head.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "the", "President", "was", "shot", "that", "--", "shot", "and", "hit", "him", "in", "the", "head", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "What did he say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Well I've been asked to open the line to the White House and to explain what was going on.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "'ve", "been", "asked", "to", "open", "the", "line", "to", "the", "White", "House", "and", "to", "explain", "what", "was", "going", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Once it was known that the President was dead, how was she in that moment and did she talk to you about it given that you were her bodyguard at that time?", "question_tokens": ["Once", "it", "was", "known", "that", "the", "President", "was", "dead", ",", "how", "was", "she", "in", "that", "moment", "and", "did", "she", "talk", "to", "you", "about", "it", "given", "that", "you", "were", "her", "bodyguard", "at", "that", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "She didn't talk to anyone really about it.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "did", "n't", "talk", "to", "anyone", "really", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Is there any real substance to why you should feel any guilt or did you feel when you went back and retraced all the movements that day from Lee Harvey Oswald to the secret service and so on that really in the end, he held all the cards and there was nothing you could do?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "real", "substance", "to", "why", "you", "should", "feel", "any", "guilt", "or", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "went", "back", "and", "retraced", "all", "the", "movements", "that", "day", "from", "Lee", "Harvey", "Oswald", "to", "the", "secret", "service", "and", "so", "on", "that", "really", "in", "the", "end", ",", "he", "held", "all", "the", "cards", "and", "there", "was", "nothing", "you", "could", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, that's exactly it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "exactly", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lee Harvey Oswald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "This I think was one of Mrs. Kennedy's first public outing since the death of her son, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "I", "think", "was", "one", "of", "Mrs.", "Kennedy", "'s", "first", "public", "outing", "since", "the", "death", "of", "her", "son", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "That's true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Kennedy"]}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Why did she do that and what did she then do?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "she", "do", "that", "and", "what", "did", "she", "then", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Well, she asked that she -- indicated she and her brother- in-law Robert Kennedy wanted to view the President's body.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "asked", "that", "she", "--", "indicated", "she", "and", "her", "brother-", "in-law", "Robert", "Kennedy", "wanted", "to", "view", "the", "President", "'s", "body", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What would you feel about the future of America and this family that you've become so close to?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "future", "of", "America", "and", "this", "family", "that", "you", "'ve", "become", "so", "close", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Well, that's one of the photographs that really reminds me how sad the occasion was.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "photographs", "that", "really", "reminds", "me", "how", "sad", "the", "occasion", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Did you ever talked to her again about the assassination or was it something you just didn't discuss?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "talked", "to", "her", "again", "about", "the", "assassination", "or", "was", "it", "something", "you", "just", "did", "n't", "discuss", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "That was a subject that either she or I discussed with each other.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "a", "subject", "that", "either", "she", "or", "I", "discussed", "with", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "But you're coming in from such a unique perspective, did any of them have any possible credence to you if you ever had a scintilla of doubt that it was just Lee Harvey Oswald acting a lot?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "'re", "coming", "in", "from", "such", "a", "unique", "perspective", ",", "did", "any", "of", "them", "have", "any", "possible", "credence", "to", "you", "if", "you", "ever", "had", "a", "scintilla", "of", "doubt", "that", "it", "was", "just", "Lee", "Harvey", "Oswald", "acting", "a", "lot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "None of them had given me any indication that they are anything but theory.", "answer_tokens": ["None", "of", "them", "had", "given", "me", "any", "indication", "that", "they", "are", "anything", "but", "theory", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lee Harvey Oswald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["John"], "LOCATION": ["Hines", "Florida", "Palm Beach", "Middleburg", "Virginia"], "PERSON": ["Mrs. Kennedy", "Caroline", "John", "Mrs. Kennedy", "Mrs. Kennedy", "Caroline"]}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "WRB", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What is your favorite moment when you look back?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "favorite", "moment", "when", "you", "look", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Well, the favorite moments are those when the four of them were together, the President, Mrs. Kennedy, and her their two children whether they were out on a boat up in Hines, Florida or down in Palm Beach and with the president and Caroline, John, and Mrs. Kennedy swimming off the boat, or out in Middleburg, Virginia where they had a country place and to Mrs. Kennedy and Caroline, and John will be riding horses and enjoying themselves and the President watching them and enjoying what they were doing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "favorite", "moments", "are", "those", "when", "the", "four", "of", "them", "were", "together", ",", "the", "President", ",", "Mrs.", "Kennedy", ",", "and", "her", "their", "two", "children", "whether", "they", "were", "out", "on", "a", "boat", "up", "in", "Hines", ",", "Florida", "or", "down", "in", "Palm", "Beach", "and", "with", "the", "president", "and", "Caroline", ",", "John", ",", "and", "Mrs.", "Kennedy", "swimming", "off", "the", "boat", ",", "or", "out", "in", "Middleburg", ",", "Virginia", "where", "they", "had", "a", "country", "place", "and", "to", "Mrs.", "Kennedy", "and", "Caroline", ",", "and", "John", "will", "be", "riding", "horses", "and", "enjoying", "themselves", "and", "the", "President", "watching", "them", "and", "enjoying", "what", "they", "were", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Kennedy"]}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CD", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "We're you very quickly aware that he was unlikely to survive?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'re", "you", "very", "quickly", "aware", "that", "he", "was", "unlikely", "to", "survive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "As soon as I walked in to trauma room one and saw him -- Mrs. Kennedy was on the left inside of the room.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "soon", "as", "I", "walked", "in", "to", "trauma", "room", "one", "and", "saw", "him", "--", "Mrs.", "Kennedy", "was", "on", "the", "left", "inside", "of", "the", "room", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "What was it like in real time?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "in", "real", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Well, I run into the end of the -- I found the open door at the end of the hospital, remarkable, you know, no one there, no security.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "run", "into", "the", "end", "of", "the", "--", "I", "found", "the", "open", "door", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "hospital", ",", "remarkable", ",", "you", "know", ",", "no", "one", "there", ",", "no", "security", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Did you say anything to them?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "say", "anything", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Well, I talked to her.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "talked", "to", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "The moment when he was pronounced dead, I mean that's a chilling moment, isn't it, for you?", "question_tokens": ["The", "moment", "when", "he", "was", "pronounced", "dead", ",", "I", "mean", "that", "'s", "a", "chilling", "moment", ",", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Did you manage to stay calm or you -- how would you describe your state?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "manage", "to", "stay", "calm", "or", "you", "--", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "your", "state", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I think we kicked in to a routine management of a coma patient.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "kicked", "in", "to", "a", "routine", "management", "of", "a", "coma", "patient", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Is there a single day that goes by in your life when you don't think of this?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "single", "day", "that", "goes", "by", "in", "your", "life", "when", "you", "do", "n't", "think", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "There are many that go by because something reminds you of it one way or the other.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "many", "that", "go", "by", "because", "something", "reminds", "you", "of", "it", "one", "way", "or", "the", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "But do you subscribe to any conspiracy theory or do you think that Oswald acted alone?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "subscribe", "to", "any", "conspiracy", "theory", "or", "do", "you", "think", "that", "Oswald", "acted", "alone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "I don't believe there's anything that we haven't heard already.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "believe", "there", "'s", "anything", "that", "we", "have", "n't", "heard", "already", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oswald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Kerry, we got this fabulous pictures, an iconic image is you playing hide and seek inside the Oval Office with President Kennedy there, and with Caroline, I think it was, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Kerry", ",", "we", "got", "this", "fabulous", "pictures", ",", "an", "iconic", "image", "is", "you", "playing", "hide", "and", "seek", "inside", "the", "Oval", "Office", "with", "President", "Kennedy", "there", ",", "and", "with", "Caroline", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Yes, that's the two of us.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "two", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Oval Office"], "PERSON": ["Kennedy", "Caroline"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "When you see that picture, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "that", "picture", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Well, it just brings back so much joy of my youngest years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "just", "brings", "back", "so", "much", "joy", "of", "my", "youngest", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Is there a plan for a family get together?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "plan", "for", "a", "family", "get", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Well, you know, our family really tries to celebrate his birthday and not his day of death.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "our", "family", "really", "tries", "to", "celebrate", "his", "birthday", "and", "not", "his", "day", "of", "death", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Is there anybody in the family as you look at it do you think could genuinely have the political drive and aspiration to perhaps one day run for president?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anybody", "in", "the", "family", "as", "you", "look", "at", "it", "do", "you", "think", "could", "genuinely", "have", "the", "political", "drive", "and", "aspiration", "to", "perhaps", "one", "day", "run", "for", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "TO", "RB", "CD", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Well, I don't know what the future is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "the", "future", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]